<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>LIFE on Ray&#39;s Personal Blog</title>
        <link>//localhost:1313/tags/life/</link>
        <description>Recent content in LIFE on Ray&#39;s Personal Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Raymon Shields</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>LIFE / PROJECT UPDATE 1</title>
        <link>//localhost:1313/p/life-/-project-update-1/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>//localhost:1313/p/life-/-project-update-1/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Life is good so far. That&amp;rsquo;s it if you want the short answer. This Post is more in lines of a Project Update instead of a LIFE UPDATE so if you want to learn more about what I&amp;rsquo;m working on then feel free to continue reading&amp;hellip; (warning this is long)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;quick-website-update&#34;&gt;Quick Website Update
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before we get started with my new job I wanted to let you all know that I will be imposing a upload schedule to my website because there is so much I want to get done. First of all because of my new work schedule I will be updating the website mainly on Monday, Wednesday and Friday. So three post a week with Monday being a main update of what happened last week, Wednesday being smaller updates and  Friday being Song Of The Week. I may still update the website with anything interesting like a new release of a game I love, interesting tech or anything else interesting. In addition at the end of the month I will release a Collection Update showing all the new games, DVDs/Blu-rays, Books and other that I acquired during that month. Along with that a Progress Report / LIFE Update will happen every two week to give updates on projects and how life is going for me. This is definitely alot to keep up with but I&amp;rsquo;m pretty sure that after a month of doing this consistently I will eventually develop a habit &amp;amp; and it would just become second nature. Anyways I won&amp;rsquo;t waste any more of your time about my website, time to talk about my new job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monday&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
          &lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wednesday&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
          &lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friday&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td&gt;Main Updates&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td&gt;Anything Else&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td&gt;Song Of The Week&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;life--job&#34;&gt;Life / Job
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve just started working as a Data Center Technician as of three weeks ago and it&amp;rsquo;s been just an influx of information thrown at me via online training. The drive to said Data Center is definitely long with a estimate time of about 2 hours to the Center and 2 hours back. But when I actual get to work with my crewmates it is great. The people here are more engaging, more willing to talk, share information, help you out and overall just talk. It&amp;rsquo;s an interesting departure from any of the other jobs I&amp;rsquo;ve worked at. I&amp;rsquo;m currently a still a trainee and my training last about a year after which I get promoted and get paid more. But no matter what the experience is worth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;main-channel--momodora-review-update&#34;&gt;Main Channel &amp;amp; Momodora Review Update
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I still need to upload a video for my personal YouTube channel even if it&amp;rsquo;s something short. I originally thought I can just upload a random video and that would be it but in the end I ended up not posting anything not knowing what to post. I&amp;rsquo;m deciding between some bowling clips or just a random video of a cat on the roof of my car. Whatever i choose i will upload it before Monday so look out for that. Other than that I decided to make a gaming channel where I post gameplay, reviews &amp;amp; anything else gaming related. I wanted to separate my personal content and gaming content because I want my family members to be able to subscribe to my channel without worrying about having to comb through the sea of gaming or collecting videos to reach a actual video.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking on my gaming channel I&amp;rsquo;m still working on my Momodora Series Review. I still trying to get use to using DaVinci Resolve along with finding new ways to express my thoughts. I haven&amp;rsquo;t had to write a essay or really express my feeling on paper/online since like High School. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to get back to writing so I can expand my vocabulary and to overall not regress in my ability to express myself. My hope is that using a median that I&amp;rsquo;m familiar with and love it makes it easier to write. So far progress is slow as I currently in the research phase, going through all the Momodora games and researching the development of each Momodora game is definitely time consuming. At the same time I been debating making one huge video review or splitting it up between 5 to 6 videos (one for each game). I&amp;rsquo;ll continue down the path of one video for now but I&amp;rsquo;ll communicate If I switch it from one to many, so stay in tune for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-projects--videos-planned&#34;&gt;Other Projects / Videos Planned
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that I&amp;rsquo;m done talking about Momodora Review I wanted to to bring up a some other project I have planned or is in the works. Just so you know not everything here is 100% going to become a Project that I&amp;rsquo;ll post publicly. Some of these projects could be mentioned here and just becomes a private project but i want to just get some stuff off my mind and onto paper (or online in this case).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-starting-a-nas&#34;&gt;1. Starting A NAS
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Network Attached Server (NAS) is a server hosted locally on your personal network that allow you to do all sort of incredible things like hosting your own Media Server, running a Minecraft Server, using HOMELAB (a software), or just as a Mass Media Drive. The main reason I want to create a NAS is to have a separate storage drive anyone can access and in order to run a Plex Server. Plex allows you to play video files hosted on your PC to anyone connect to the network / account. The Plex Server alone is worth it because using my PC&amp;rsquo;s Blu-ray player I can extract my DVD/Blu-ray content and have my own personal Netflix at home. For example If I have Breaking Bad on blu-ray I can rip it using my blu-ray player like I&amp;rsquo;m ripping a Music CD and sort the episodes so that I can add it to Plex and access the show without have to pay for a Subscription service [Plex is Free]. This is allows me to access the uncompressed Blu-ray rips for TV Shows &amp;amp; Movies rather than going through a streaming service that will compress and degrade the quality because It has to serve all these video to so may customer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main thing holding me back thou is easily the cost of everything. In order to host the huge amount of Data I demand I would need more than 36TB configured in RAID 2 (RAID 2 = 18TB of storage with another 18TB working as a fail-safe in case I lose data). This includes all my DVD/Blu-ray rips, raw  video &amp;amp; audio recordings (real life and game recordings), ripped Video Game Disc (PS3, GameCube, Wii &amp;amp; More) &amp;amp; Project Files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each DVD disc is 4.7 GB extracted, Blu-ray disks are anywhere from 20GB - 50 GB &amp;amp; 4K Blu-rays are 50GB-100GB. I will use a Handbrake in order to get rid of any padding &amp;amp; compress the file without any major quality loss. And even then these files can still be upwards of 10GB. So for this project I will be using Enterprise HDD (Hard Disk Drives) using &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://serverpartdeals.com&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://serverpartdeals.com&lt;/a&gt;. I chose to use Server Part Deals because all the Drives are rated for use in Data Centers &amp;amp; will last longer than a regular off the shelf HDD. But as you can see the price in of itself is an investment The drives alone don&amp;rsquo;t account for the fact that I still need to build a separate PC with 10GB Networking and enough processing to run 4K content and anything else I throw at it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll stop here but I may make a separate post in order to get real in depth on how ripping Blu-rays work and encoding. Thanks for bearing with me though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-comptia-certs&#34;&gt;2. CompTIA Certs
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This one is a short one but I want to go ahead and get my other CompTIA certs. I already have my Security+ 601 (acquired in &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jan 2024&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;) but I wanted to go back and get my other certs since they are technically easier than the Security+. In order from easiest to hardest I will be getting my: &lt;strong&gt;Tech+, A+ (Part 1), A+ (Part 2), Networking&lt;/strong&gt;.
&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.comptia.org&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://www.comptia.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-collection-video&#34;&gt;3. Collection Video
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not mention in my YouTube section is that I also have plans on doing a full Blu-ray collection showcase with context on why I bought certain show and movies. This is something I want to create for a while but I need a few things before this project becomes a reality. I already made a deal with my brother for his Sony camera but I would still need to learn how to use it and how to create stable shots and manage multiple video files. This is another reason I&amp;rsquo;m making my Momodora Review video, because it helps for getting ready to manage multiple clips especially since I can see my Collection Video being broke up easily into three or more multi-hour long videos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-love2d&#34;&gt;4. LOVE2D
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This project is something I&amp;rsquo;m doing mainly for fun &amp;amp; is just a private project but I wanted to mention it as it&amp;rsquo;s something I&amp;rsquo;ve used before but I wanted to create a small RPG Game just to put some of my ideas into a game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://love2d.org&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://love2d.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 
 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h3 id=&#34;this-took-way-too-long-to-make--i-will-try-to-keep-my-post-shorter-in-the-future&#34;&gt;This took way too long to make &amp;amp; I will try to keep my post shorter in the future.
&lt;/h3&gt;</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
